Hello Hello!
We are in Hammarby Sjöstad in Stockholm, and what should we do?
- Bake!
- Yay!
A while ago we got an email from a guy named Albin.
His father is a baker and is called Magnus.
His bakery & pastry is there!
Here!
- They should teach us to bake.
- Hopefully something very miserable.
We will bake pastries and croissants.
- Yes!
I love croissants.
And pastry.
- It will be super good.
See what a lot of butter.
Now we will have about 1044 layers of butter, dough, butter, dough ... so they get crispy and good.
- How big will they be?
- It depends on how big you make them.
What did you say?
- 1044 layers exactly?
- Stay here.
No Harry, absolutely not!
- May I count them?
- Yes, you have to do that when we eat them.
We have rolled so, and then we turn it in this direction, and we will do the same again.
- Who is going to drive now, then?
- Alma!
Alma, beware!
Now we must be careful so that we do not destroy the layers.
Okay Alma, then we press here.
- Pull a little in the dough too.
- Good.
A little more.
Get to know, do you have muscles here?
Yes, you had.
Then we do this, oh hi oh.
- Fold the snibber under.
- I want to do that.
Good.
Now these are going to ferment for about an hour and a half.
Okay.
- Sad, huh?
- Yes.
- Then we have to sit and roll our thumbs.
- It's lucky that I have ice cream then, right?
Yes!
Albin will ask today's question when eating ice cream.
"What countries have Alma and Harry been in?"
Good question.
Do you remember?
- Jamaica.
- Malaysia.
There are a total of ten countries that Alma and Harry have been in, with Sweden.
Yes!
- What a good bill.
We have never counted ourselves.
- No, but I think it's actually true.
Move some Harry, so Alma comes out.
Here comes the Tuffe-Tuffe train!
TUT-TUT!
They crashed.
TUT-TUT-TUT!
Pang!
- In the middle of the cake.
- Stylish holes.
Move down your hand, Alma.
- So there.
- Oh!
Oh!
Well!
- What did you do?
- She threw a piece of chocolate!
- Did she eat a bit?
- Yes.
It is okay.
Do you remember, now we have done the three -stroke, the lighthouse and the three -stroke, right?
Check out what many layers, do you see?
Oh.
The best thing about pastry and when you rolled and so, do you know what to do then?
The best of all.
Oh.
It's crispy and then it melts ... mmm!
Do you want to taste?
Harry?
Oh!
- Beware my fingers.
- Yes.